[Music]
foreign
again i returned to the fight
i will not falter
i will not waste this chance
let us hope for a different outcome
much better i am
healed i am repaired
i'm on fire my warrior spirit
burns
[Music]
strength flows through me
i am unstoppable
damn yoshi
most enjoyable it was nothing
it is an honor our enemies return
you've rescued me again dr ziegler
genji here genji is with you
[Music]
sniper be wary
i have spotted the enemy enemies hide it
enemy turret ahead
enemy teleporter detected
our enemies possess a teleporter
i found the teleporter our enemies have
deployed a shield generator
behind you watch yourself
take cover big three throws in here
defend defenders one
victory is near the battle draws to its
conclusion
we must attack time is against us
press on our point is under attack
let us welcome our guests
opponents under attack let us rid
ourselves of these unwanted guests
we are losing the objective push them
back
our enemies have the upper hand for now
let us
turn the tables i am taking the
objective
join me the objective is mine
be quick about it
we must press our advantage and see its
fixed tree
the payload is stopped and here i
thought we had a plan
push that payload
push forward
the pain or the moves we must keep it
safe
keep the payload in motion
stop the payload the payload is moving
stop it we need to stop the payload
converge upon it i learned that
from my brother like cutting through
silk know yourself in the face of death
think upon your actions an excellent
fight
foreign
i am victorious this time brother
mock death at your own peril
i have the upper hand this time master
my aim is an airing
destroyed the enemy teleporter is no
longer our concern
migoto master
angela
will avenge you brother
hello yo
greetings thank you
arigato i understand
very well understood
i need healing i require healing
up group up here
join me my ultimate is charging
my ultimate is almost ready
my blade is ready to be unleashed
my ultimate is ready
the dragon and i are one
a steady blade balances the soul
measure twice
[Music]
foreign
you are only human
i was hoping for a challenge
my halloween costume cyborg ninja
yo merry christmas
to know yourself is to be at peace
kind of you seem nice
i hate to kill you
the sword is an elegant weapon for more
civilized age
that's right wait used to
hey where did they all go
it is not too late to change your course
brother
so this is what has become of you
a pity
that was your dream not mine
we shall see brother
i am certain of it what would our father
think of what we've become brother
why don't we find out
i am a different man now i
am whole i got you some chocolates genji
swiss they're the best thank you angela
perhaps you could share them with me
angela
i have some chocolates for you not swiss
i suppose it will have to do thank you
gandhi
i find the company more agreeable these
days
i am at peace with who i was your threat
does not concern me our paths
cross for now as to the future
we shall see
i always liked working with you winston
no awkward small talk
the heart of a man still beats inside me
does the suffering of the omnics here
trouble you master
it is good to fight alongside one of my
brightest
pupils
you master
that was another life
i pass many an hour of my misspent youth
here
ramen it's just not the same anymore
just setting fruit here sets my soul at
ease
only here do i not feel outcast
this is my home now
this is my sword ryuichimonji
even here i feel an odd test
it is beautiful here i could never
appreciate it before
torsha gaijin let's say then
are you singing
[Music]
let's say then dancing
okay
the demon becomes me
genji's here
fantastic technique
break the limit
unbreakable body
any chocolates today brother
the winds of death are strong
i still have much to learn
you